[{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974927729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":17312,"timeElapsed":80007},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974938005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":10275,"timeElapsed":90283},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974947511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":9505,"timeElapsed":99789},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974954912,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":7401,"timeElapsed":107190},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974958633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3719,"timeElapsed":110911},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974971393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":12757,"timeElapsed":123671},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974980566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":9171,"timeElapsed":132843},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975010816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":30249,"timeElapsed":163094},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975021454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":10637,"timeElapsed":173732},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975072275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":48951,"timeElapsed":224553},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975078085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":5809,"timeElapsed":230363},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975088932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":10846,"timeElapsed":241210},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975095097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6163,"timeElapsed":247375},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975100841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5744,"timeElapsed":253119},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975108300,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":7455,"timeElapsed":260578},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975115369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":7068,"timeElapsed":267647},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975126339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":10970,"timeElapsed":278617},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975131577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5237,"timeElapsed":283855},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975166438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":33592,"timeElapsed":318716},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975169459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3020,"timeElapsed":321737},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975171710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2250,"timeElapsed":323988},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975177226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5515,"timeElapsed":329504},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975180248,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3021,"timeElapsed":332526},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975187948,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7699,"timeElapsed":340226},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975192352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4403,"timeElapsed":344630},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975200859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":8506,"timeElapsed":353137},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975204038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3179,"timeElapsed":356316},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975222799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":17779,"timeElapsed":375077},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975227192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4392,"timeElapsed":379470},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975231776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4583,"timeElapsed":384054},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975235901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4125,"timeElapsed":388179},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975243893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":7991,"timeElapsed":396171},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975251250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":7356,"timeElapsed":403528},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975257569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6318,"timeElapsed":409847},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975264999,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7430,"timeElapsed":417277},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975275836,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":10836,"timeElapsed":428114},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975280773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4936,"timeElapsed":433051},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975300223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":18258,"timeElapsed":452501},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975306373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":6149,"timeElapsed":458651},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975310531,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4157,"timeElapsed":462809},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975316059,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5528,"timeElapsed":468337},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975319851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3791,"timeElapsed":472129},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975327667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":7815,"timeElapsed":479945},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975335797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":8129,"timeElapsed":488075},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975346843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":11043,"timeElapsed":499121},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975349495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2651,"timeElapsed":501773},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975359603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":8845,"timeElapsed":511881},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975367571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":7967,"timeElapsed":519849},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975374839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7267,"timeElapsed":527117},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975380863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":6023,"timeElapsed":533141},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975383287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2423,"timeElapsed":535565},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975390299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":7011,"timeElapsed":542577},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975393787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3487,"timeElapsed":546065},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975402078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":8287,"timeElapsed":554356},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975406295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":4216,"timeElapsed":558573},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975426553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":19133,"timeElapsed":578831},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975431855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":5301,"timeElapsed":584133},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975436101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4245,"timeElapsed":588379},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975440205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4103,"timeElapsed":592483},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975445065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4860,"timeElapsed":597343},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975452911,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":7845,"timeElapsed":605189},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975458385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5473,"timeElapsed":610663},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975464368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5981,"timeElapsed":616646},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975469951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":5582,"timeElapsed":622229},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975484413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":13536,"timeElapsed":636691},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975488219,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3805,"timeElapsed":640497},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975494456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":6237,"timeElapsed":646734},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975497942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3485,"timeElapsed":650220},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975504046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6103,"timeElapsed":656324},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975508305,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4258,"timeElapsed":660583},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975516341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":8036,"timeElapsed":668619},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975521071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":4729,"timeElapsed":673349},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975526840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5767,"timeElapsed":679118},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975529680,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2840,"timeElapsed":681958},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975546846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":15905,"timeElapsed":699124},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975550524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3678,"timeElapsed":702802},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975553636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3111,"timeElapsed":705914},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975563352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":9713,"timeElapsed":715630},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975569688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":6335,"timeElapsed":721966},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975577000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":7312,"timeElapsed":729278},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975580110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3109,"timeElapsed":732388},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975585339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5226,"timeElapsed":737617},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975587977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2638,"timeElapsed":740255},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975600751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":11644,"timeElapsed":753029},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975607553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6801,"timeElapsed":759831},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975611745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4192,"timeElapsed":764023},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975618129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":6383,"timeElapsed":770407},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975621765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3635,"timeElapsed":774043},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975632103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":10338,"timeElapsed":784381},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975635482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3378,"timeElapsed":787760},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975641883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":6400,"timeElapsed":794161},{"subjectID":"ovmd9aypzn","prolificID":"6082c902e76a87571f42e73e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d07f6daae6e1a643689","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975644102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2217,"timeElapsed":796380}]